tauntr.com 2011-03-16

# Privacy Policy | TAUNTR.COM

## **Privacy Policy: Your Privacy Rights**

**Effective Date: September 18, 2009**  

**Last updated: September 18, 2009**  

We created Tauntr (the “Web Site”) to provide sports fanatics with a forum to create and exchange jokes, taunts, insults, and other parodies related to professional and college sports.  When it comes to your privacy, however, we take things seriously.   

This is our Privacy Policy.  It tells you what information we collect when you visit our Web Site, how we use, share and protect that information, and how you can access and update that information. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you are not allowed to use the Web Site. By using the Web Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Personally Identifiable Information**  

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “personally identifiable information” means information that identifies a particular individual, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, and phone number. Other information, such as your IP address, cookie information, clickstream data, and software and hardware attributes, is not “personally identifiable information,” unless it is directly associated with other personally identifiable information. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  

In addition to information you choose to provide to us, we also collect non-personally identifiable information through technology to make our site more interesting and useful to you. Tauntr may use this information for any purposes that it deems appropriate, in its sole discretion.  We may also combine this information with personally identifiable information that you have provided to us and/or with other information that is publicly available or that we receive from other reputable sources in order to make our Web Site and communications more targeted to your interests 

**Collecting and Using Information**  

Tauntr collects personal information when you register, when you use certain Tauntr products or services, when you visit pages on the Tauntr Web Site or the pages of certain partners, and when you enter promotions, contests, or sweepstakes.  

Tauntr automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request. 

Tauntr collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners. 

Tauntr uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.  

**Registration**  

You can browse the Tauntr Web Site and use many features without registering or providing information about yourself.  Other features and activities, such as sending taunts to others or contributing content, require you to register or provide some information about yourself.   

  1. When you send taunts or other content to others, we ask for certain information, including your email address, your friend’s email address, your hometown, and your favorite sports team. 

  2. Premium Members must register and create an account on our Web Site. To create an account you are required to provide information, including your name, physical address, email address, phone number, and credit card and billing information, which is personally identifiable information that allows Tauntr and others to identify you.

When you register with Tauntr and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

In addition, we may combine personally identifiable information that you have provided to us with other information that is publicly available or that we receive from other reputable sources. 

Tauntr is for users 18 years of age and older.  Minors (under the age of 18) are not permitted to use our Web Site and should not submit any personally identifiable information to us. 

**Customer Service**  

Tauntr may collect information through the Web Site in order to, among other things, accurately categorize and respond to a customer’s inquiry and deliver appropriate service levels. 

**Cookies**  

Like most websites, Tauntr uses cookies and web log files to track site usage.  A cookie is a small amount of information that is sent from a web server to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. Tauntr uses cookies to verify that you are properly signed in and to display information consistent with your settings, for example.  Tauntr may also use cookies from time to time to measure your response to new aspects of the Web Site and/or emails in an effort to continually improve customer service and Web Site usability.  

You can erase or block cookies from your computer if you wish to do so (your internet browser help screen or manual will thoroughly explain this process), but certain Tauntr services, as well as parts of the Web Site, may not work correctly or will not work at all if your browser is set not to accept cookies.  

**Web Beacons**  

Web pages may contain electronic images (called a “single-pixel GIF” or “web beacon”) that are used to count users who have visited that page, or to access certain cookies.  

Information about your visits to this site, such as the number of times you have viewed an ad may be used to serve ads to you. In addition, we may share Web Site usage information about visitors to our sites with our web advertising partners for the purpose of managing and targeting advertisements and for market research analysis on our site and other sites.  Once you have clicked on an advertisement and left our Web Site, our Privacy Policy no longer applies and you should read the privacy policy of the advertiser to see how your personally identifiable information will be treated on its site. **]**  

**Tauntr Communications**  

Tauntr will communicate with you through email and notices posted on our Web Site or through other means available through the Tauntr service.  Please be aware that you will always receive certain emails from Tauntr related to the proper functioning of your account, such as email notices when another user sends you a message. Tauntr may also send you promotional information unless you have opted out of receiving such information (see ‘Opt-Out Procedures’ below).  

**Protecting and Sharing Personal Information with Third Parties**  

Tauntr is committed to its users’ privacy.  Tauntr uses commercially reasonable means to protect the confidentiality of personally identifiable information provided by users, including technological, administrative, and/or physical safeguards.   

Tauntr does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

  1. We will share your personally identifiable information with trusted partners to carry out or to provide specific services or information. For instance, we may use a credit card processing company to bill Premium Members for subscription fees. These third parties may retain, share, or store any personally identifiable information so as to provide these services.

  2. We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 

  3. If we believe, in our sole discretion, that it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Tauntr's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

  4. We transfer information about you if Tauntr is reorganized, acquired by or merged with another company, or in connection with a sale of assets to another person or entity.  Any third party to which we transfer or sell Tauntr’s assets will have the right to continue to use the personally identifiable information and any other information that you provide to us under the terms of Tauntr’s then-applicable privacy policy.  Tauntr or its successor will notify you before information about you becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

Tauntr may display targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria—for example, men ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. Tauntr does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.  

These advertisers may include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies). 

**Personally Identifiable Information Contained in User Content**  

  Some sections of our Web Site may allow users to post or transmit messages, comments, screen names, computer files and other materials. Tauntr does not monitor such transmissions, and therefore cannot be responsible for any personally identifiable information or other information that may be contained in such transmissions.

**Links to Other Sites**  

  We may provide links on our Web Site to other sites. These sites operate independently of Tauntr and have established their own privacy and security policies. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read these policies at any site you visit. 

**  Disclosure of Use of Personal Information** 

You can request that Tauntr tell you which of your personally identifiable information it maintains and the means through which Tauntr obtained such information, by contacting Tauntr at **[**[copyrightagent@tauntr.com](mailto:copyrightagent@tauntr.com) **]**.  Upon receiving your request, Tauntr will respond after it confirms that the request has been made by you personally.  

**Accessing and Changing Your Account Information**  

You can review the personally identifiable information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information you publish, or to the settings for your Tauntr account including your email, and contact preferences, at any time by logging in to your account on the Tauntr website. Please be aware that even after your request for a change is processed, Tauntr may, for a time, retain residual information about you in its backup and/or archival copies of its database. 

**Closing Your Account**  

You can also close your account through the Web Site. If you close your Tauntr account, we will remove your name and other personally identifiable information from our publicly viewable database. We may retain certain data contributed by you if we believe it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. To request that we close your account and remove your information from the Web Site, please send your request to [accounts@tauntr.com](mailto:accounts@tauntr.com). Please send your request using an email account that you have registered with Tauntr under your name. You will receive a response to requests sent to [accounts@tauntr.com](mailto:accounts@tauntr.com) within five business days of its receipt. 

**Opt-Out Procedures**

**   
**When you register, we will ask you for your marketing preferences.  You can opt out of having your personal information shared with third parties for marketing purposes or from receiving marketing and promotional materials from Tauntr.  You can also edit your marketing preferences at any time to opt out of receiving such marketing materials.

From time to time, new categories of marketing communications might be added to the marketing preferences page. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.  

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Tauntr service, such as service announcements and administrative messages that are considered part of your Tauntr account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.  

You can also opt-out by sending an email to [optout@tauntr.com](mailto:optout@tauntr.com) or written mail to: 

Tauntr    
46 Plympton St.

Boston, MA 02118  

Please include your name, email address and the specifics of your request. However, after you opt-out we or our trusted partners may continue to contact you via email for administrative or informational purposes, including follow-up messages regarding the administration of your account, any services, features or functions you have enrolled in or registered to use, any Promotions you have participated in or have entered, goods and/or services you have ordered, or other transactions you have undertaken with the Web Site. 

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**  

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will always be posted to this section of the Web Site, along with the effective date of the new policy. All users should check this Privacy Policy page periodically to stay abreast of any such changes.  

**Questions and Suggestions**  

If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at:

Tauntr   
46 Plympton St.

Boston, MA 02118

617-728-0037

**_CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS_**

**   
**Residents of the State of California have the right to request a list of all third parties to which a company conducting business in California has disclosed personally identifiable information during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, the law provides that if the company has a privacy policy that gives either an Opt-out or Opt-in choice for use of your personally identifiable information by third parties for marketing purposes, the company may instead provide you with information on how to exercise this choice. 

Tauntr qualifies for this alternative option: it has a comprehensive privacy policy and provides you with details on how you may either Opt-out or Opt-in to the use of your personally identifiable information by third parties for direct marketing purposes (see ‘Opt-Out Procedures’ above).  Therefore, we are not required to maintain or disclose a list of the third parties that received your personally identifiable information for marketing purposes during the preceding year.
